Ice! I need more ice!
冰块! 我还要冰块!
Comin' up.
马上来
Chris, buddy.
Chris 伙计
I need help man. I don't feel good.
我需要帮助 我觉得很不舒服
I'm in Chinatown somewhere, some alleyway.
我在唐人街的某个地方 某条小巷里
I need you to come pick me up.
我需要你来接我
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 玩火 第一季第8集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 玩火 第一季第8集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：毛线君爱提提
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：瑜香 校对：酒囊饭袋 时间轴：毛线君爱提提
We should probably get some sleep, don't you think?
我们真的应该睡一会儿的 你觉得呢
Yeah, we should probably get on that.
是啊 我们最好现在就开始
What? What?
怎么了? 怎么了?
So which is it?
所以我们这样算什么?
Am I your boyfriend, or is this just... you know.
我是你男朋友 还是...这只是...你知道的
Are we having "the talk"?
我们现在就要谈这件事吗
I'm just saying.
我只是随口一问
Yeah, you're right, I mean...
好吧 你是对的 我是说...
We're in the same unit.
我们在同一个队上班
It's against the rules.
这是违反规定的
It has to stop.
我们必须做个了断
Tonight's the last time. Ever.
今晚是最后一次
You're so full of it.
真是拿你没办法
We can't tell anyone, Jesse.
我们不能告诉任何人 Jesse
Moreland, Rebecca.
不管是Moreland还是Rebecca
Yeah. Done.
嗯 好的
We're good liars, right?
我们真是撒谎的个中好手 对嘛?
So all we have to do is lie.
所以我们要做的就是对所有人撒谎
Ben Trinder. Twenty-one years old.
Ben Trinder 21岁
Coroner did a tox screen.
验尸官做了毒性测试
He was positive for GHB and get this, liquid nicotine.
GHB和液体尼古丁测试结果呈阳性
Seriously? That stuff's lethal.
真的? 这两样东西混在一起可是致命的
GHB is a party drug.
GHB是一种派对上常见的毒品
It's low-tech, made in basement labs.
技术含量很低 在地下实验室里生产
Drug Squad's best guess is dealers add in the nicotine to pump up the high.
缉毒组认为毒贩很可能把它加入了 液体尼古丁用来促进药效
So what, they overshot, put in a little too much?
所以呢 他们放过头了 量加得太多了?
If there's a bad batch of drugs out there, things can get real ugly.
如果有一批药在市面上流通的话 事情可能会变得很糟糕
Remember a few years ago that dealer that was cutting coke with novocaine?
记得几年前有个毒贩子尝试 把可卡因加进麻醉药里么?
Yeah, eight people died and thirty more in I.C.U.
是啊 死了8个人 还有30多个进了重症监护室
So we need to move fast, before we end up with more dead kids.
所以我们需要行动起来 在更多的孩子因此送命之前
So what we got?
我们有什么线索?
Not much, a location. Before he died, he went to a place called Stem.
不多 一个地址 在他死之前 去了一个叫做Stem的地方
It's an illegal after hours club.
是一家非法的地下酒吧
Never heard of it. I've been there.
- 从来没听说过 - 我去过
It moves around every few months to avoid getting busted.
每隔几个月他们就会搬地方 以防被抓到
Word of mouth, invitation only.
靠的是口口相传 没有邀请不得入内
See John, basically, if you're over thirty...
看吧 John 基本上来说 如果你过了30岁...
Drug Squad doesn't want to do a raid, they think it will spook the dealer.
缉毒组不想进行突袭 他们不想打草惊蛇
He'll disappear into thin air, and the drugs stay out there.
否则毒贩就会消失在空气里 而毒品则会继续留在市面上
So they're handing the case over to us.
所以他们把这个案子交给了我们
The owner of Stem is Joe Kane.
Stem的老板叫Joe Kane
He's gone down twice for assault, once with a broken bottle, took out someone's eye.
因为伤人被捕过两次 其中一次用了个碎瓶子挖出了一个人的眼珠子
This guy's got a temper.
这家伙脾气够火爆的
Guaranteed, he's going to know who the dealers are and who's selling.
谁说不是呢 他应该知道毒贩是谁 谁负责出货
Drug Squad sent this over, it's an invitation card.
缉毒组送过来的 是张邀请函
We use it to get by the doorman.
我们得用它来通过门卫
Jesse, you're under thirty, you can take point.
Jesse 你没到30岁 你去吧
See if you can get inside and get an idea on this dealer.
试试看能否进去 然后找出谁是毒贩
Cool.
没问题
Why don't I go with him? I've been there before, I know the scene.
不如我跟他一起去吧? 我之前去过 知道里面什么样
You wanna go undercover? They grow up so fast.
- 你想当卧底? - 孩子们成长得真快啊
Hey, I've done plays before.
嗨 我以前做过的
Small ones. But, yeah, good idea,
是很小的行动 但是 好吧 这主意不错
Let's unleash you into the world.
咱们把你放归大千世界
The entrance to the club is in a Chinese restaurant on Spadina.
俱乐部的入口在Spadina街的一家中餐馆
According to Drug Squad, you go through the restaurant into the kitchen.
根据缉毒组介绍 你要穿过中餐馆的厨房
There's a stairway in back. It'll take you down to the club.
后面后个楼梯 走下去就到俱乐部了
You'll both be wired.
你们俩都会带上窃听
Maria and John will run cover. They'll be right upstairs.
Maria和John会支援你们 他们就待在楼上
Private party tonight.
今晚是私人派对
Seriously? This card doesn't work?
没搞错吧? 这卡不能用?
Not tonight, man. Turn around.
今晚不行 小伙子 转身出去吧
What about this? This help?
这个呢 能帮上忙吗
It's a private party, bro. Sorry.
这是个私人派对 伙计 抱歉
OK, so... What's it going to take? Look, it's not happening, alright?
- 要怎么样才能进去? - 你进不去的 明白吗
So turn around, stop wasting my time.
所以麻烦你转身出去 别浪费我时间了
I don't think Joey would be very happy with you turning away pretty girls.
像你这样拒绝美女入场 我想Joey看到了恐怕会不高兴的
You know Joe do you?
你认识Joe?
I used to go to these parties all the time. Oh yeah?
- 我以前一直参加那些派对的 - 是嘛?
So what does Joe hang on top of the DJ booth at every location?
那么Joe在每个地方的DJ台上面挂的都是什么?
Dude she was high, she wasn't paying attention.
老兄 她当时正嗨着 哪里会注意到这些啊
No, no, no, I got this. It was a... sign.
不 不 不 我记得的 是个...招牌
It's one of those scrolling... "Don't Stop Love. "
是那种有滚动文字的..."不要停止去爱"
Am I right?
我说得对吗
I'm totally right. I got two coming down.
- 我说的一点都没错 - 有2个人下来了
Thank you so much. Don't stop the love, baby.
多谢 不要停止去爱 宝贝儿
Okay they're in.
好了 他们进去了
Do you really know that guy, Joe the owner? Nope. Never met him.
- 你真的认识那个人吗 Joe 那个老板? - 不认识 从没见过
Your job is to ID the dealer, that's it.
你的任务是找出毒贩 这就够了
You're looking to score. Talk to waiters, bartenders, the owner if you see him.
你们要找的是毒品 跟服务员 酒保聊聊 如果见到老板 也跟他聊聊
Be careful. Anyone smells you're a cop, the dealer will vanish.
小心点 如果有任何人察觉出你是警察 毒贩子就会消失的
What can I get you? Beer and a vodka soda.
- 喝什么? - 啤酒和伏特加
Behind you. Is that Joe?
在你身后 那是Joe吗
I don't know. It's hard to tell without the bruises
我不知道 没了那些淤青之后认不大出来了
Let's get a closer look.
咱们走近点瞧瞧
You know what, it should just be me.
这样吧 我一个人去行了
I can get closer to him without you.
没有你 我能跟他靠得更近一些
Wait just a sec.
等等
I'll be careful. Girlfriend?
- 我会小心的 - 你女朋友?
Yeah. No, it's complicated.
是 也不是 有点复杂
So you're a dick.
所以你是个混蛋咯
No.
不是
I want her to be my girlfriend, I just have to convince her.
我想让她成为我的女朋友 我只是得让她点头
Good, I hate dicks.
很好 我恨混蛋
Joe, hi.
Joe 你好啊
I love the new building.
我喜欢这个新地方
You don't recognize me, do you?
你不认得我了 是嘛?
Seriously? You're one of those guys, huh?
不是吧? 原来你跟其他男人一样 是吧?
Khali. Khali, right.
- Khali - Khali 没错
What's happening? Khali's ID'd the owner.
- 怎么了? - Khali找到了店老板
Nice try. Give me a break, I meet a lot of beautiful women.
- 做得不错 - 让我歇一下 今晚遇到了太多的美女了
Oh right, good save.
哦 好的 补救得不错
Cheers. Cheers.
干杯
So who do I talk to if I want to party?
所以如果我想要尽兴的话 应该找谁?
Just point me in the right direction and push.
你给我指个正确的方向 推我一把呗
She's blunt as hell. You want to party.
- 她也太直接了 - 你想要尽兴
The direct approach.
单刀直入
No one's ever told you to say no to drugs, little girl?
从来没有人告诉过你要远离毒品吗 小姑娘?
Not even once.
一次都没有
Wish I could help you out, I just can't do that.
我真希望能帮到你 不过我爱莫能助
Really?
真的?
Sorry.
很抱歉
You're a photographer, right?
你是个摄影师 对吗
Yeah.
嗯
Are those yours?
这些是你拍的?
You like? Are you kidding?
- 你喜欢? - 你开玩笑吧?
I love, they're amazing. Thank you.
- 简直是爱死了 看上去美极了 - 谢谢
Are you a photographer? I always wanted to be.
- 你是摄影师吗 - 我一直想要成为一名摄影师
Maybe you could give me some pointers.
也许你能教我几招
What would you like to know? What does this do?
- 你想要知道点什么? - 这是干嘛用的?
You want another beer?
要再来杯啤酒吗
Will you do a shot with me? Two shots of vodka. One for you.
你能陪我喝一杯吗 两杯伏特加 请你喝一杯
I'm Jesse.
我叫Jesse
Beetle. What?
- Beetle(甲壳虫) - 什么?
Like the bug.
就是那虫子的名字
There's gotta be a guy around here who's selling, right?
这里肯定有个人在四处兜售 对吧?
I'm looking to score.
我想要搞点毒品
Is what I'm saying, hoping you could help me.
我想说的是 你能帮我搞点儿吗
I wish I could, but our guy's not in tonight.
爱莫能助 这人今天不在
Nothing gonna do with you.
没办法
Really?
真的?
You look so disappointed. Thanks for the drink, Jesse.
你看上去很失望的样子 谢谢你的酒 Jesse
Let's go. Aliright.
- 咱们走 - 好的
What's going on? Joe's confirmed the dealer's not in the house.
- 发生什么事了? - Joe确认了毒贩今天不在这儿
Is Khali going somewhere with that guy? I've got a bad feeling about this.
Khali是不是要跟那家伙到别的地方去? 我有种不祥的预感
He's got an apartment upstairs, he's going to show her some photos.
他在楼上有间公寓 他准备给她看些照片
I want you to stay with them, okay? I don't like it either.
我要你跟着他们 好么 我也觉得有事儿要发生
But we got ears. We're going to let this one play. Don't lose her.
但是我们有监听 我们走一步看一步 不要跟丢了
I'm right behind them. They're going in back.
我就在他们后面 他们正往后面走
All right. Stay with them, OK? Done.
- 好的 跟着他们 明白么? - 好的
Is this a good idea? She'll get more from him when they're alone,
- 这是个好主意么? - 他们独处的时候 她能从他那儿套出更多的东西
then with a bit of luck, the dealer might make a house call.
然后如果足够走运的话 毒贩也许会送上门来的
You okay?
什么事?
I lost her. Bouncer won't let me through.
我跟丢了 保镖不让我进去
Alright, just get back up here fast.
好的 马上回到这里来
Well, it's kind of mess but...
那个...里面有点儿乱 但是...
come in, come in, make yourself at home.
进来 进来 你自便
Wow, this place is great.
看呐 这地方太棒了
She's inside.
她在里面
Third floor, apartment six.
3楼 6号公寓
Have some drinks, look at some photos, then I have a surprise for you.
喝两杯 看看照片 然后我有个惊喜要给你
Surprise, what is it? You're going to like it.
- 惊喜 是什么? - 你会喜欢的
???
Jesse
What are we doing?
我们要怎么做?
On the third floor there's a fire escape, let's go.
三楼有个逃生通道 我们走
If anything bad happens, you know what to do, alright?
如果有任何不利的事情发生 你知道该怎么做的 对么
I got it, get up there, hurry.
明白 你们去吧 快点
Let me just pull this up. Be my guest.
让我把这个打开 你自便
Oh wow, these are amazing.
这些太漂亮了
Look at how you captured all those people.
看看你的镜头是怎么捕捉到这些人的
That's what I do.
我就是这么做的
What are you pouring me? A big fat cocktail.
- 你在给我倒什么? - 一大杯鸡尾酒
You trying to get me loaded or something?
你是要把我灌醉还是怎样?
Then I'm going to take advantage of you.
然后我就会占你便宜
Good luck with that.
那就祝你好运了
John, hurry. I don't like what I'm hearing. A little of this...
- John 快点 他们的对话让我觉得很不舒服 - 一点点的这个...
Alright, and...
对 还有...
Be right there...
马上就来...
You are so talented.
你真是太有才了
This is amazing. Thank you.
这个太美了 谢谢
Cheers. Cheers.
干杯
So, I have something for you. A little gift.
好了 小姑娘 我有东西要给你
Hold out your hand.
伸出你的手
Best way to get to know someone.
了解一个人的最佳途径
You get high with them.
有了它们 你就能嗨起来
You get right 'under their skin'.
它们会成为你身体的一部分
John, he's offering her drugs.
John 他在给她毒品
We're almost there.
我们马上就到了
How is she? She's holding her own, but you gotta move.
- 她怎么样了? - 她目前还能坚持 但是你必须得快点
Where do you get this stuff, you got a dealer?
你从哪儿搞来的这玩意儿? 你认识毒贩?
Don't worry about it, just enjoy, alright.
这个你不用担心 尽情享受就行
I want to.
我想要
I just feel so bad for ditching my friends like this.
但是就这么甩了我的朋友 让我觉得很不好意思
You can't call. Have you ever had GHB before?
你不能打电话叫他们一起来 你之前有试过GHB吗
This stuff is very pure, very clean, it's very designer.
这东西非常的纯 很干净 档次很高
Just like liquid E.
就跟液体摇头丸一样
My friends are going to want me downstairs. So I...
我的朋友会想让我下楼去的
Stay a little. Let me help you out here.
再待一会儿 不如我来帮你吧
Open your mouth, open your mouth.
张开嘴 张开嘴
You know what I'm going to have to bail.
我要去尿尿
What I don't get it? Thanks for the drink.
- 什么 我没听明白? - 谢谢你请我喝酒
How can I talk you into staying?
我要怎么说才能让你留下?
Why are you freaking out on me? We're just having drinks.
你为什么好像很害怕我的样子? 我们只是在喝酒而已
Hey! Things are getting tense.
- 嗨! - 情势变得紧张了
Where are you?
你们在哪儿?
We're at the top. The door's locked!
我们在顶楼 门被锁住了!
Hey, get off me!
嗨 放开我!
What makes you think you're going to leave?
你凭什么觉得自己想走就能走?
She's in trouble. Get in there, get her out.
她有麻烦了 快进去 把她救出来
Get off me! I wanna go!
放开我! 让我走!
You wanna party? We're gonna party, you little bitch.
你想要尽兴是吧? 那咱们就进行到底 你个小婊子
Police!
警察!
Get off her!
放开她!
Khali?
Khali?
She's OK. She's OK.
她没事
Jesse, that's enough.
Jesse 够了
You OK?
你没事吧?
I got him.
我抓住他了
Right there, yeah.
就在那儿
He was trying to get me to take GHB.
他想要让我喝下GHB
Then he slams me up against the wall. It came out of nowhere.
然后他把我推向墙壁 事情发生得很突然
But I'm fine, it's fine. It's fine.
但是我没事 没事
You're not fine. Your lips.
你有事 看看你的嘴唇
It's okay.
没事的
It doesn't hurt.
不觉得疼
You're going to drive her to the hospital anyway, get it checked out.
不管怎么样 你送她去一趟医院 做个检查
We need the medical report, you know that.
我们需要医疗报告 你知道的
I'm fine. Don't argue.
- 我没事 - 别争了
Look, this was a tough situation, you did good.
听着 今天的状况很危险 但是你做得很好
Come on.
来吧
What's going on?
发生什么事了?
This just came in. Tyler Clarke.
刚刚收到的 Tyler Clarke
Twenty years old. GHB laced with liquid nicotine.
20岁 GHB和液体尼古丁
We got another overdose on our hands.
我们手上又多了一个吸毒过量致死的
I thought he was going to kill you.
我还以为他会杀了你
You were in there with him, and I couldn't get to you.
你跟他待在一起 然后我没办法靠近你
Hey. I'm okay. It's okay.
嗨 我很好 没事的
No it's not okay! That was brutal.
这样不好! 刚才的事很残忍
You nearly blew our cover with Rebecca, you know.
你差点就在Rebecca面前穿帮了 你知道么?
I don't care.
我不在乎
You're really upset.
你好像真的很生气
You just figured that out now?
你现在才看出来?
I'm getting blood on you.
我把血弄在你脸上了
C'mon on, I'll drive.
来吧 我开车
This is entrapment. I was set up.
你们这是诱捕 给我设的局
Yeah? How's that?
是嘛? 怎么说?
Those weren't my drugs, they were hers.
那些毒品不是我的 是她的
She must've brought them up to my place, happens all the time.
肯定是她带到我家去的 这事儿很常见
I didn't touch her, she attacked me, I was defending myself.
我没有碰她 她攻击的我 我只是在自卫
Joe. It's her word against mine.
- Joe - 是她冤枉我
Who knows, maybe you'll get lucky. Maybe the judge'll believe you.
天知道 也许你会走运的 也许法官会相信你的说辞
At this moment, I couldn't care less.
但是此刻 我毫不关心
Ben Trinder, Taylor Clarke.
Ben Trinder Taylor Clarke
Both of these kids bought drugs at your club.
这两个孩子都是在你的俱乐部买的毒品
GHB, you know all about it. We found a dozen caps in your kitchen.
GHB 你都知道的 我们在你家厨房找到了十多支
It killed them. These kids were barely twenty.
是它杀了他们 这些孩子才20来岁
Maybe they got them somewhere else,
也许他们是从别的地方搞到的
All right, cause I don't allow drugs in my club. That would be illegal...
明白么 因为我的俱乐部们不允许有毒品 那样是违法的...
I'm not in the mood to play games... I don't care what the hell you're in the mood for, lady!
- 我没心情跟你玩游戏... - 我他妈的也不在乎你有心情干什么 女士!
You drag me down here, you throw all this crap at me.
你把我搞到这儿来 把这些东西都怪到我头上
If anymore of these drugs get sold... That's not my problem!
- 如果这些毒品还在继续出售... - 那关我屁事!
I have done nothing wrong!
我什么也没有做错!
Now can I please make my phone call?
现在我可以打电话了吗
We got nothing from Joe Kane, but we're holding him, for assault and running an illegal bar.
从Joe Kane嘴里一无所获 但是我们会拘留他 罪名是伤人和经营非法酒吧
A second OD has been linked back to the club. Same cause of death.
这家俱乐部已经有了两起吸毒过量事件了 死因相同
I should warn you. I'm getting big pressure from the brass.
我要警告你们 上头给了我很大的压力
They want to shut the club down.
他们要关闭俱乐部
That's a bad idea, it'll just pop up somewhere else.
这是个坏主意 它会在别的地方再冒出来的
They're giving us 24 hours to get this done.
他们给了我们24小时来了结这件事
What? You're kidding me.
什么? 你开玩笑吧
You wanna show us the spoils of your evening?
- 要给我们看看昨晚你拿到的东西吗 - 嗯
I grabbed over a 1,000 photos from Joe's laptop.
我从Joe的笔记本里抓了一千多张照片
So far, fifteen of them, from fifteen different nights.
目前为止 找到了15个人 在15个不同的夜晚出现过
This guy, he's in the background.
这个家伙 他在照片的背景里
Standing in one spot and people coming up to him.
站在一个地方 然后人们上前去找他
That looks like a buy if I could see their hands.
看上去像是在做交易 如果我能看到他们的手的话
We need a name, that's not gonna come from our friend Joe.
我们需要知道名字 但是咱们的朋友Joe 恐怕是不会告诉我们的
The bartender, Beetle. You got an angle?
- 那个酒保 Beetle - 你找到了切入点?
She likes nice guys.
她喜欢好男人
I'm thinking I could be a little heart broken.
我在想我可以装成心碎的样子
That's our best move. Okay, so I'll head back into the club.
- 这是咱们最好的机会了 - 好吧 那么我回俱乐部去
Not you. You got the night off.
你不用了 今晚你休息
We should also be working the street. Check with your CI's maybe they've heard something.
我们也应该去街上查查 看看你们的线人们有没有听到什么风声
We need to get this dealer now.
我们需要马上找到这个毒贩
Khali, got a second?
Khali 你有时间吗
Can you shut the door?
能把门关上吗
How's your face? It's hurting.
- 你的脸怎么样了? - 还在疼
Hypothetical.
假设性的问题
If two of my officers were becoming personally involved,
如果我的两个手下开始私人交往
it would be a problem for me. I'd have to follow procedure.
对我来说就会成为一个问题 我不得不根据规定来做
Transfer one of them out of the unit.
把其中的一个人调离本单位
If they were. Yeah.
- 如果他们在交往的话 - 是的
That kind of emotion, you can't think clearly.
如果有了那种情感 你就无法清晰思考
This isn't a game Khali, kids are dying.
这不是一场游戏 Khali 有孩子正在死去
You make bad choices, you get distracted.
如果你做出错误的选择 如果你被分散注意力
You put everyone's life in danger.
那么就会将所有人置身于危险之中
I wouldn't want that to happen. Me either.
- 我不希望看到那样的事情发生 - 我也不想
Do I need to have this talk with anyone else?
这个对话我还需要跟另外一个人进行吗
No, you're good.
不 不必了
I've done some crazy-ass things to impress her.
我做了很多疯狂的事情 为了取悦她
This is the girl from last night?
就是昨晚的那个女孩子?
This one time in high school... this is kinda embarrassing.
高中的时候 有一次... 这事儿还挺丢人的
You did something stupid.
你做了件蠢事
I wanted to show her how agile I was so I jumped out of a window and I broke my leg.
我想让她看看我有多灵活 于是我从窗口跳了出去 然后摔断了腿
But it worked, big time. So you're sweet, huh.
- 但是起作用了 轰动一时 - 所以你很贴心 对吧
That's how you get laid, by being a sweetheart?
你就是这么把姑娘们搞上床的 当个贴心的小男人?
Should try being hardcore, see if girls like that better?
应该试试当个硬汉 也许姑娘们更喜欢那样的?
No, no, stick with sweet, sweet is good.
不用 不用 保持贴心就行 贴心的男人不错
So where is she tonight, your soulmate?
那么她今晚在哪儿 你的灵魂伴侣?
I don't know, she's probably out cheating on me.
我不知道 也许在什么地方背着我跟别人搞
What, that's funny?
怎么了 你觉得很好笑?
She's banging some guitar player. This guy wrote a song for her.
她跟一个什么吉他手搞上了 那家伙给她写了一首歌
How am I suppose to compete with that? You got out-sweeted.
- 我要怎么样才能比得过那样的男人? - 看来贴心这招不好使了
The way this night is going, I need to get high.
今天晚上 我要嗨一把
I need to get completely messed up.
我需要彻头彻尾大醉一场
I should not be doing this.
我不应该这么做的
Mention my name, and he will hook you up, okay.
提我的名字 然后他会帮你搞定的 明白么?
Off I go. You're the best. Watch yourself, okay?
- 那我去了 你最棒了 - 你自己小心点 明白吗
Liam's a little crazy. No sudden moves around him.
Liam有点疯狂的 不要突然出现在他边上
Help! We need help in here! This guy isn't breathing!
救命! 这里需要人帮助! 这个人没有呼吸了!
I don't know. He just keeled over, right in front of me.
我不知道 他就在我面前倒下了
Hey. Are you OK?
嘿 你没事吧
Can you talk? Did you call an ambulance?
你能说话吗 你叫救护车了吗
Yeah, I'll call back and see how far they are.
有 我再打一个 看他们还有多久到
Mark!
Mark!
What happened to him!? You know this guy?
他怎么了!? 你认识这个人?
What did he take? Who gave it to him?
他吃了什么? 谁给他的?
I don't know. I just came in, he was lying on the ground.
我不知道 他就这么躺在地上
Mark, wake up! Oh God, what did he take?
Mark 醒醒! 天呐 他吃了什么?
I need help, emergency, in the men's washroom, now!
我需要帮助 紧急事件 在男洗手间 马上!
His name is Mark Cameron. He was DOA at Mount Sinai.
他的名字是Mark Cameron 在Mount Sinai当场死亡
Three OD's. Three different nights. All from the same club.
三个吸毒过量致死的 三个不同的夜晚 在同一家俱乐部
The bouncer seemed to really take it hard.
那个保镖似乎很受打击
Take a look at this, it's Mark's phone.
看看这个 是Mark的手机
That's the other two victims. So they knew each other, all three of them?
这是那两名遇害者 所以他们互相认识 他们三个人?
They were all friends?
他们是朋友?
They partied together, had the same dealer? Presumably Liam.
他们在一起玩 所以毒贩子应该也是同一人? 应该是Liam
Okay, but wait.
好的 但是等等
The night he died, Mark got a text.
他死的那晚 Mark收到了一条短信
"Hey, baby, you should come to Stem tonight, I'm partying, dying to meet you. "
"嗨 宝贝 今晚你来Stem吧 我在参加派对 很想见到你哦"
Came from a burner cell, it's impossible to trace.
从一次性手机发的 无法追踪来源
And check out Ben's phone, two nights earlier.
再看看Ben的手机 两天前
("Hey, baby, you should come to Stem tonight, I'm partying, dying to meet you. ")
(嗨 宝贝 今晚你来Stem吧 我在参加派对 很想见到你哦)
Same text word for word. They were lured to the club.
- 一模一样的短信 - 所以他们是被引诱到那个俱乐部去的
Someone is targeting these boys, one by one.
有人把目标对准了这些男孩 一个接一个
We're dealing with multiple murders.
我们在处理的是多重谋杀案
OK, Danny, we need to find Liam and make a buy.
好了 Danny 我们得找到Liam 然后跟他作笔生意
We need to bring him in for questioning.
我们要把他带回来问话
You got it. I'm on the third floor now.
明白了 我现在正在三楼
Tell me what you see. Looks like a sweatshop, must be at the back.
- 告诉我你看到了什么 - 看上去像是家服装厂 他们肯定在后面
Be careful, Beetle said he's crazy.
小心点 Beetle说他有点疯狂
So this should be fun then?
所以这次应该会很有意思咯?
Hey, I'm looking for Liam.
- 嗨 我要找Liam - 那边
Drug Squad's following up with the families of the boys.
缉毒组那边在跟进男孩的家属们
Maybe they know something. Ben Trinder has a sheet.
- 也许他们知道点什么 - Ben Trinder有前科
Possession for the purpose, two counts.
两次 非法持有
So what, these guys are in the drug business?
所以这些家伙也参与了毒品生意?
Honing in on Liam's turf and he didn't like the competition, and decided to take them out?
侵蚀着Liam的地盘 然后他不喜欢有人来竞争 于是决定干掉他们?
It's possible. Could be a motive.
有可能 这可能是个动机
Hey, I'm Daniel. I'm the one that called.
嗨 我是Daniel 打电话的那个人
Daniel from the suburbs, how you doing?
郊区来的Daniel 你好吗
I'm out.
我不玩了
Come over here, let's talk over here.
过来  咱们过来谈谈
Listen...
听着...
I heard you could help me out, maybe. You heard that, huh?
- 我听说你可以帮到我 也许 - 你听说了 是吧?
I could make it worth your while, man.
你会觉得很划得来的 老兄
I'll take everything you got right now.
你手上所有的东西 我都会买下
You want to talk about it or should I turn around?
你想要谈谈 还是我应该扭头走人?
You're a friend of Joe's? Yeah.
- 你是Joe的朋友? - 没错
I like Joe. He's a stand-up guy.
我喜欢Joe 他是个有担当的人
Really? I think he's a dick.
是吗 我觉得他就是个混蛋
This guy's a comedian.
这家伙很有喜感
Can I show you something?
我能给你看些东西吗
Look at this, I just got this, it's like four hundred years old.
看看这个 我刚得来的 差不多有四百年的历史了
Are you a cop, Daniel?
你是警察吗 Daniel
'Cause if you are, I'm going to gut you with my antique knife.
因为如果你是 我会用这把古董刀 把你的肠子掏出来
Goes in like butter, that's how sharp it is.
- 白刀子进 红刀子出 - 就是这么锋利
I know.
我知道
I already tried it, on the last cop who wanted to be my friend.
我已经试过了 在上一个 想要跟我交朋友的警察身上
Let's relax, alright?
咱们放松点 好嘛?
If I was a cop, you'd be in cuffs right now.
如果我是警察 你这会儿就已经戴上手铐了
You're scared.
你害怕了
Oh boy, you're scared.
好家伙的 你害怕了
What are you doing, man?
你这是在干什么 老兄?
Are you putting a hole in my shirt? Is that what you are doing?
你是要把我的衣服弄出一个洞来吗
You know how much this shirt cost?
你知道这件衣服多少钱么?
Oh man, I wrecked it.
哦 不好意思 我把它弄坏了
Look, Joe said you had good stuff, and I'm buying in bulk.
听着 Joe说你这里有上等的货 我要批量购买
So if you think I'm a cop, then I'll go buy my stuff somewhere else.
所以如果你觉得我是警察 我去别的地方买就是了
From someone less paranoid, maybe.
从某个不那么疯癫的人手里 也许
What's that mean:
你说的批量
"bulk".
是指
Two liters to start?
2升起售?
OK, Khali, what have you got?
好的 Khali 你有什么发现?
Lab reports.
实验室报告
The blood work from Mark Cameron is a match.
Mark Cameron的血检报告是匹配的
All three boys died of the same thing. GHB?
3个男孩都是因为同样的东西致死
Same bunch of GHB.
同一批GHB
It's identical and matches what Crazy Liam sold to Daniel.
这跟疯狂Liam卖给Daniel的东西 是完全一致且匹配的
Except for one thing.
除了一样东西
The nicotine.
尼古丁
Yeah. What Daniel bought wasn't laced, it was clean.
是的 Daniel买的那些是未经混合的 是纯的
So Liam was lacing the individual caps.
所以Liam把它们分装成单独的一小支
Targeted killings. He wanted to take out his competition.
有目的的杀人 他想要在竞争中获胜
We should talk to the bouncer, Orlando.
我们应该跟那个保镖谈谈 Orlande
When Mark was on the floor there, his reaction? I think he knows them.
当看到Mark躺在地上时 他的反应? 我想他应该认识他们
Makes sense if these boys want to take over Liam's business.
有道理 如果这些男孩子想要接手Liam的生意
Orlando worked there, he could be involved.
Orlando在那里工作 他可能也牵涉其中
I'm going to go pay him a visit. See if he can fill in some blanks.
我去拜访一下他 看他能不能给我们填补一些空白
You wanna have a go at Liam there? Yeah.
- 你想要去跟Liam谈谈么? - 好的
No.
不要
I don't want you, I want the cop that tricked me.
我不要跟你谈 我要那个耍了我的警察
Why don't you go out there and get him and bring him back
不如你出去 找到他 然后让他进来
cause I got a couple of things I want to say to him.
因为我有好些事情想要跟他说
You finished? 'Cause I got some bad news for you, Liam.
你说完了? 我有一些坏消息要告诉你 Liam
Trafficking was bad enough, but now manslaughter.
毒品交易已经够糟糕了 现在还加上了过失杀人
You're screwed.
你完蛋了
What the hell are you talking about?
你他妈的在说些什么?
Oh you know. Those GHB caps you're selling at the Stem,
你卖到Stem的那些GHB
you've been cutting them with poison, liquid nicotine.
你把它们混合成了毒药 液体尼古丁
No, I'm not. Oh yes, you are.
- 不 我没有 - 有 你有
Three dead kids, Liam, that's not good.
3个死去的男孩子 Liam 这可不妙啊
Whoa, whoa, just stop!
噢 噢 别说了!
Just think about it for a second.
你自己想一想
A, I'm an artist, alright, I take pride in my work.
首先 我是个艺术家 明白吗 我为自己的工作感到骄傲
B, I'd be killing off my own clientele.
其次 我这么做客户都会跑掉的
What? You think I'm trying to put myself out of business?
什么? 你以为我会自己断了自己的财路?
I don't know, maybe you're trying to put them out of business.
我不知道 也许你想断的是他们的财路 你不知道你在说什么
What are you talking about? Were those kids stepping on your turf, Liam?
那些孩子是不是在蚕食你的地盘 Liam?
Look. Any one of my customers could have done it.
听着 我的任何一个客户都有可能做这件事
Do the math, hundreds of kids in that club.
你自己算算吧 俱乐部里有几百个孩子呢
Then you tell me, which one did it Liam?
那不如你告诉我到底是谁干的吧 Liam?
My lawyer, right now, before I say another word.
我要见我的律师 马上 在此之前我什么都不会说的
Let's get this kid a lawyer.
给这小子找个律师
He's going to need one.
他会需要律师的
Good morning, Orlando. Rebecca Ellis, Detective Sergeant.
早 Orlande 我是警探Rebecca Ellis
I have a couple of questions for you. About what?
- 我有几个问题想问你 - 关于什么的?
Your friend, Mark.
你的朋友 Mark
He died at the hospital. I'm sorry.
他死在了医院里 我很抱歉
Yeah... come in.
哦...进来说吧
So you're crashing at Joe's place?
所以你现在住在Joe的家里?
Yeah, he got arrested. I'm looking after it for him.
是啊 他被捕了 所以我替他看家
How'd you know I was here? I'm the one who arrested him.
- 你是怎么知道我在这里的? - 逮捕他的人是我
Did you know these two boys as well?
你也认识这两个男孩吗
Tyler Clarke and Ben Trinder. No.
- Tyler Clarke和Ben Trinder - 不认识
I mean, yeah they came to the club. They OD'd.
我是说 对 他们去过俱乐部 他们吸毒过量了
That's all I know.
我知道的就是这些
Who gave them the GHB?
是谁给了他们GHB?
Who wants them dead Orlando? They were dealing drugs maybe? Pissed someone off?
谁想让他们送命 Orlando? 也许他们在贩毒? 惹怒了某人?
C'mon you work at the club, you see things.
你在俱乐部工作 肯定看见了不少事情
Like I said...
就像我之前说的...
They come to the club, they like to hang out at the club.
他们来俱乐部 他们喜欢在俱乐部里玩
We're friendly, that's it.
我们互相都很客气 仅此而已
And what else?
还有什么?
Nothing.
没了
Orlando, you know something about this.
Orlando 你还知道点别的
Tell me what happened.
告诉我发生了什么
You'll feel better when you do.
说出来会让你觉得好过一点的
No I won't, believe me.
不 我不会的 相信我
I can't stop thinking about it. What did you see?
- 我无法不去想这件事 - 你看见了什么?
Something bad.
糟糕的事
Something very, very bad.
非常非常糟糕
There's this stock room, in the club, in the back.
俱乐部的后面有一间储藏室
And there's a girl. Bro, you in or out?
- 然后有个女孩 - 兄弟 你参加还是退出?
It was Ben, the guy that died, that OD'd.
是Ben 就是吸毒过量死掉的那个
Ben Trinder?
Ben Trinder?
Yeah. And Mark was there too.
是的 Mark当时也在场
And they were... They were taking off her clothes.
他们在脱她的衣服
Who is she?
她是谁?
I don't know, man, some girl, named Sadie.
我不知道 伙计 某个女孩呗 叫Sadie
So you in or out?
你参加还是不参加?
And I did nothing.
然后我什么也没做
I went to the bar.
我去了酒吧
I got shots, I got wasted.
我拼命喝 喝得酩酊大醉
I saw the girl come out, Sadie.
我看见那女孩走了出来 Sadie
She looked bad, she was crying.
她的样子很糟糕 她在哭
I don't know who she was, I never saw her at the bar before.
我不知道她是谁 我从来没在酒吧里见过她
I should've done something, I should have. I should have... why didn't I call the cops?
我应该做些什么的 我应该...我为什么没有报警?
Why didn't I go in there, myself?
我为什么没有冲进去?
How many guys were in the room with Sadie?
和Sadie在一起的有几个男的?
Five... five.
5个...5个人
Mark, Tyler, Ben, and two more.
Mark Tyler Ben 还有2个
I don't know them.
我不认识的
Orlando, someone's targeting these boys.
Orlando 有人把目标对准了这些男孩
If there's two out there...
如果还有2个人...
I'm sorry, I don't know their names.
很抱歉 我不知道他们的名字
Look, I'm telling you the truth.
听着 我说的都是实话
Sadie what? No last name.
- Sadie 姓什么? - 不知道姓氏
Just pull up sexual assaults in the last month.
调出上个月的性侵案
Nothing. She probably didn't report it.
没有 她很可能没有报警
Do a general search. Girls, 16 to 24, first name starts with "S"...
那就做个模糊搜索 女孩 16至24岁 名字是S开头的...
Okay. There's like five hundred.
好的 差不多有五百个结果
What?
怎么了?
Sadie Jansen.
Sadie Jansen
Oh God, she committed suicide two weeks ago.
天呐 她两星期前自杀了
Hanged herself. Who called it in? Does it say?
- 上吊的 - 是谁发现的? 记录上有吗
Her parents were out of town, she was found by...
她爸妈当时不在城里 是被她的...
What?
什么?
Her sister. Brynne Jansen.
她姐姐发现的 Brynne Jansen
Nickname, Beetle.
昵称Beetle
She's targeting the boys who raped her sister.
她把矛头对准了强奸了她妹妹的那些男孩
So she buys the drugs, adds the nicotine,
所以她买了那些毒品 加入了尼古丁
lures them into the club, spikes their drinks.
引诱他们到俱乐部 然后诱骗他们服下
Makes it look like an OD. So it's revenge, pure and simple.
- 让事情看上去像是吸毒过量的样子 - 所以是复仇 简单清晰
And she has two more targets out there. She could poison them any minute.
她还有两个目标没有除掉 她随时有可能对他们下手
We got names? We're not there yet.
- 我们知道名字了吗 - 还不知道
Why don't we just pick her up? Have you talked to Homicide?
我们为什么不直接抓她? 你跟凶杀组谈过了吗
She's not at home, she's not answering her phone.
她不在家 也不接电话
Besides, we don't have enough evidence, not yet.
再说 我们没有足够的证据 还没有
Jesse you're going to the club tonight, you and Khali.
Jesse你今晚去一趟俱乐部 你和Khali一起去
We need to get a confession. Okay? All right, let's get this done.
我们要让她认罪 明白吗 好了 咱们去把事情了结了
It's going to be all hands on deck tonight, including Khali, everyone has ears.
今晚所有的人都会出动 包括Khali 大家都带上耳机
Jesse will take point.
主要由Jesse去做
John and Daniel will be upstairs in the restaurant for back up.
John和Daniel在楼上的餐厅里 作为支援
Maria and I will be in the van.
Maria和我会在车里
We're good, we got audio.
没问题 有音频了
She's not at the bar.
她不在吧台那里
You wanna hang back for a second?
你稍微等我一下
I'm looking for Beetle. You and me both.
- 我在找Beetle - 我也在找
She's not working tonight?
她今晚不上班?
When you find her, tell her to get back here, I need help.
如果你能找到她 告诉她回来上班 我需要她帮忙
She's here somewhere.
她在这里的某处
She's gone AWOL.
不知道躲到哪里去了
Okay, let's take a look around.
好了 咱们四处看看
Khali, you need to search the entire club.
Khali 你需要搜查整个俱乐部
Orlando mentioned a stock room, see if you can find it.
Orlando提到了一个储藏室 看看你能不能找到
No sign of her yet, we're going to split up.
还没看到她 咱们得分头行动
I found her.
我找到她了
Beetle's in the stock room. What's she doing?
- Beetle在储藏室里 - 她在干什么?
Sitting there, on the ground. She's looking pretty rattled.
坐在那儿 坐在地上 她看上去很慌乱的样子
I just keep thinking.
我一直在想
If somebody I care about got hurt, if I could picture that.
如果某个我在意的人受到了伤害 如果我能想象那个场景的话
How I'd feel.
我会有什么样的感觉
That's good, Jesse, use it, try and get a confession.
很好 Jesse 利用这个 试试看能否让她认罪
You've got five minutes, if it doesn't work, we arrest her on the evidence we have.
你有五分钟 如果不起作用 我们就以现有的证据逮捕她
Which isn't much, so give me your best shot.
但是不太充分 所以你要尽最大努力
I'll be right outside.
我就在外面
Oh sorry, I didn't know you were in here.
哦 抱歉 我不知道你在这儿
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
I just ran into my ex again. From that night, I told you?
你刚才碰见我前女友了 就是那晚上我跟你说过的?
She was with that guy, again. The guitar player.
她又是跟那个男的在一起 那个弹吉他的
Sorry, I just... I need a second.
对不起 我只是...只需要一会儿
You can't stay here, you should go.
你不能待在这儿 你应该离开
I just need a drink. You wanna do a shot?
我只想喝一杯 你想来点儿吗
To tell you the truth, you look like you could use one.
跟你说实话吧 你看上去很需要来一杯
Sorry, it's not my business.
抱歉 我知道不关我的事
That guy with Khali, he's bad news.
跟Khali在一起的那个男人 不是什么好东西
I can tell.
我看得出来
I keep getting these pictures in my head.
我的脑海里一直浮现着这样的画面...
If he ever hurt her...
如果他敢伤害她...
I'd go crazy.
我会发疯的
You'd get mad.
你会很生气的
Hell yeah.
说的一点都没错
How mad?
会有多生气?
Honestly? If he hurt her bad?
说实话 如果他把她伤得很重?
The way I feel about her.
让我这么感受到了
I don't see how I wouldn't lose control.
我肯定会失去控制的
You wouldn't be able to think,
你会没有办法思考
or breathe.
或者呼吸
Exactly.
没错
It would take you over.
它会将你淹没
Sounds like you've been there before.
听上去你像是过来人
Yeah. What makes you say that?
是啊 你是怎么看出来的?
Because I've been there before.
因为我也曾经历过
It's true. I've done some bad things.
是真的 我做过一些很糟糕的事
What happened, Beetle? Did you do something?
发生了什么 Beetle? 你是不是做了什么事?
My little sister.
我的妹妹
A bunch of guys got her drunk and high and...
有一群人把她灌醉了 然后...
they hurt her.
伤害了她
Yeah? How bad?
是嘛? 有多严重?
They raped her.
他们强奸了她
Right here, right in this room.
就在这里 就在这间屋子里
And I wake up every day thinking,
每天我醒来都在想
all I want is for those guys to be dead.
我要让那些人偿命
Alright here we go.
好了 来了
But you're not that big, though. You don't have to be.
可是你并不强壮啊 你不必是
How would you do it?
你会怎么做呢
The thing about poison is, they don't know what's happening to them.
下毒的好处在于 他们不知道自己发生了什么
You don't get to tell them why you're killing them.
你不必告诉他们你为什么要杀他们
But this last guy,
但是最后的这个家伙
I told him.
我告诉了他
I said "You raped Sadie"
我说 你强奸了Sadie
And he begged and cried.
然后他拼命求饶 还哭了
Who did?
谁做的?
Who begged and cried?
谁又求饶又哭泣?
Did you do something? Where is he?
你是不是做了什么? 他在哪儿?
I shouldn't have told you.
我不应该告诉你这些的
Beetle, where is he?
Beetle 他在哪儿?
Is he in there?
他在那里面吗
Stay back, stay back! Put it down. Take it easy.
- 退后 退后! - 把枪放下 放轻松
John, get in there. There's weapon in play.
John 快进去 里面有武器
Oh, God. Khali, stay where you are.
- 天呐 - Khali 待在原地
I will shoot you. I want him dead. Put it down.
- 我会开枪的 我要让他死 - 把枪放下
He stays in there until he's dead!
他会待在那儿 直到死神降临!
Get back, stay right where you are!
退后 给我待在原地
Get back! Get Back! Beetle!
- 退后 退后 - Beetle
Khali! Khali!
Khali! Khali!
Beetle.
Beetle
Beetle, You don't know me.
Beetle 你不认识我
I'm a cop, Beetle.
我是个警察 Beetle
So is Jesse. We're undercover cops.
Jesse也是 我们是卧底警察
Khali, out of here, go, get out.
Khali 离开那儿 走 出去
Are there more cops outside? Are there more cops outside?!
外面还有更多的警察吗 外面是不是还有其他警察?!
Yes, yes there are. Beetle, please just put down the gun.
是的 外面有 Beetle 求你了 把枪放下
If they come in here, I will shoot him.
如果他们敢进来 我就开枪打他
I don't care, I will kill him. You tell them that.
我不在乎 我会杀了他 你去告诉他们
Okay, okay. I don't care.
- 好的 好的 - 我不在乎
OK, I'll let them know. Listen to me.
好的 我会告诉他们的 听我说
I know that your sister got hurt.
我知道你的妹妹受到了伤害
That those boys hurt her in the worst way, and that she took her life.
那些男孩用最恶劣的方式伤害了她 然后她了结了自己
Are you trying to talk me down now or something? You kidding me?
你是想要说服我吗 还是什么? 你想耍我是吧?
That's what I'm supposed to do, but I've never done this before, so...
我应该是要这么做的 但是我之前从来没做过 所以...
Shut up!
闭嘴!
OK, OK, alright, alright. Alright.
好 好 好的
John, it's escalating, are you close?
John 事件在升级 你快到了吗
Almost there.
马上到了
Get out! Go!
出去! 快走!
Just listen to me, okay?
听我说 好吗
I came in here not because I'm a cop,
我进来不是因为我是个警察
but because I...
而是因为我...
I love him.
我爱他
I'm in love with him and no one knows.
我爱上他了 但是没有人知道
None of the people we work with, not even him.
没有任何一个同事知道 包括他自己
So if you... if you hurt him,
所以如果你...如果你伤害他
I'll be exactly, where you are right now,
那么我就会成为和你现在一模一样的人
with the person I love dead and gone.
所爱的人死亡 离去
And I'll be in all the pain you're in.
然后我也会经历你所承受的这些痛苦
So I'm asking you, not because I'm a cop,
所以我请求你 并不是因为我是个警察
but because I don't want to lose him.
而是因为我不想失去他
I love him, please.
我爱他 求你了
Please.
拜托了
Please Beetle. It's alright.
拜托了 Beetle
It's OK.
没事的
Police! Don't move!
警察! 不许动!
Where is he? Where is he?
他在哪儿? 他在哪儿?
Call an ambulance.
叫救护车
Thought maybe you could use a drink after today.
我想着今晚你可能会想要喝一杯
Thanks.
谢谢
At least we saved that boy's life, that's something, right?
至少我们救了那孩子的命 这也算是点成绩了 对吧?
Cheers.
干杯
So Jesse and Khali, what's happening between those two?
那么Jesse和Khali 他们俩发生了什么?
It was just Khali working the target.
Khali只是想要拿下目标人物而已
Whatever it took. Good.
- 所以随便说什么都行 - 好
'Cause relationships in the same unit,
因为在同一个单位里谈恋爱
they never work.
是从来都行不通的
No. No.
- 行不通
You know, you saved my life today, I think. That's right.
- 你知道么 我想你今天救了我的命 - 没错
You owe me big time.
你欠我一个很大的人情了
So...
那么...
Did I mean everything that I said?
我之前说的是不是真心话?
Yeah.
嗯
Or was it just a way to talk down Beetle?
或者只是你用来说服Beetle的说辞?
You know that I like you.
你知道我喜欢你的
You know... we gotta stop this, right?
你知道...我们得停止这么做了 对吧?
And we will.
我们会的
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入